I'm sorry... I... I...
I put the secret elixir of the sea
in Prince Aquasteed's tea!
Don't cry, Icilla.
Stop! Look at me!
Prince Aqua!
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
My Beautiful Lady
Prince Aqua?
Prince Aquasteed.
Everything is ready.
We must hurry to the ocean.
I can't believe I spoke
to Tiara in that voice.
Oh. Tiara, you can wait here
at the castle if you want.
I'm the worst man alive!
You can say that again!
So how is that love potion
actually affecting you?
It's calmed down compared to before,
but I'm still in trouble
if I see Lady Icilla.
My heart is wavering.
But I love Tiara so much...
I want to say the name of the one I love,
but I feel like another name
will slip out.
Just what is love, anyway?
I'm the only one who's all alone.
Wow. How long has it been
since it was this bad?
About 700 years.
What are you gonna do?
You're basically the entire
cause of it this time.
I dislike the woman called Tiararose.
She has some nerve leading Claire on.
King Pearl said that
Lady Tiararose is leading you on.
If Pearl really did say that,
maybe I can hold
on to the tiniest shred of hope.
Though I can't just come out
and ask, "You were jealous?"
Hey, Keith.
I just had a great idea.
Would you help me with it?
What?
This is your problem.
Why do I have to clean up after you?
Fine. Just this once.
I had a feeling you'd say that.
Oh, really? So what do you want me to do?
We're moving too quickly!
Let's rest for a bit!
I'm fine!
Prince Aquasteed!
Is this an effect of the drug?
I know in my head
that it's inconceivable,
but my body thirsts for Lady Icilla.
Let's return to the castle for now.
In that condition, you can't...
No.
I have to get to the ocean,
whatever it takes.
Prince Aquasteed...
Prince Aqua!
Tiara?
Yes, it's me.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry!
No. It's because of the love potion.
It's not his fault.
Tiara...
Your Highness!
Your Highness...
Icilla.
Please don't, Prince Aqua!
Please, Prince Aqua...
Would you indulge my
selfish whims once more?
I...
I love Prince Aqua more than
anyone in the world!
Tiara?
How could I do something so ridiculous?
Damn it!
Prince Aqua?!
No... Prince Aqua!
Tiara!
The sweet voice he always uses...
I can't believe I let a drug overtake me.
I'll never forgive myself
for being so spineless.
You aren't spineless at all!
Thank you.
It's pitch-black.
I didn't realize it was this bad.
Aquasteed.
Tiara.
You're finally here.
Tiararose, I'm sorry Pearl's
caused so much trouble.
I also failed to be attentive enough.
King Pearl isn't the only one to blame.
Soon you will feel
the same pain that I feel.
King Pearl is hurting.
Even if it's a misunderstanding,
it's my fault.
You look like you're in pain.
What happened?
You're even wounded!
That...
is all my fault.
I forced His Highness to drink
the secret elixir of the sea.
Secret elixir? You don't mean Pearl's...
That little...
She's so hopeless.
The drug's effects shouldn't last long,
and Pearl should have the antidote.
Then I'll go see her right away!
You can't.
This ocean is dangerous, even to us.
If a human like you goes in,
you'll never last.
I am prepared for that.
Lady Icilla, you mustn't!
But...
You don't need to worry about me,
but we can't leave
the ocean in this state.
I realize that this is a problem
that the humans and sea fairies
should resolve together,
but since we don't know how
to return the ocean to normal,
you're the only ones we can depend on.
Would you please lend us your aid?
I beg you.
I'm begging you, too!
I want our beautiful ocean to come back!
Tiara, do you know
why there are three fairy kings?
No, I don't.
So that if one of us
loses their way, suffers,
and warps nature,
the rest of us can right it.
To be precise, humans blessed
by the other two fairies must fix it.
Is that really true?
You, Aquasteed,
have received my blessing,
and Tiararose has received Keith's.
If the two of you use your magic,
you can restore the ocean.
I see...
What?
I-I can help heal this vast ocean?
Yes.
But I don't have enough magic power!
Prince Aqua does,
but my magic is not enough!
You don't have a choice.
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
My magic can heal this ocean?
Do major events like this
really happen to villainesses?
It'll be fine. Can you trust me?
Prince Aqua...
Prince Aqua indulged my selfish request.
Now it's my turn to believe in him.
Claire.
I bestow the blessing of the Sky Fairy
King upon Aquasteed Marinforest.
I'm putting my hopes in you,
and your strength
as this nation's future king.
Um... Keith?
I bestow the blessing of the Forest Fairy
King upon Tiararose Lapis Marinforest.
I'm right here. You need only
keep your eyes facing forward.
It's all right, Tiara.
I'm right beside you.
This is my power we're talking about.
There's no way you can fail.
Prince Aqua... Keith...
I feel better now.
I mean, I can't even
imagine these two losing.
Let's do this, Tiara.
I'll lend you my power.
Call forth the trees and purify the ocean.
Right!
Trees of the forest, lend me
the power to protect this kingdom.
Amazing... This is the power
of the Forest Fairy King?
Blast it! Tiara's magic
isn't strong enough!
I knew it. Because I'm not the heroine...
Hey!
Do you think we could use these cookies?
They have my magic in them.
Oh?
Yes, it'll work.
I can feel magic
coursing through my body.
Trees of the forest, please!
These trees will absorb
the contaminated water.
That just leaves...
I'm here with you,
so you have to protect the ocean.
Come on, Aquasteed!
Put more of your magic into it!
I know.
Wind, bring light to this black ocean!
It's beautiful!
You did great.
Prince Aqua, could it be...
Yes, it seems the drug's
effects have worn off.
Your magic entered my body
through the cookie I ate.
That must be why.
I'm so glad!
Tiara, I love you.
Thank you for believing in me.
I should be thanking you.
I'm so glad we were able to
heal the ocean together.
Tiara?
Oh, it's nothing.
Prince Aqua is dripping
with handsomeness!
But this Prince Aqua is mine alone.
Your hand is so warm, Tiara.
I'm sorry for touching you
with my wet hand!
I'd like you to do it more, actually.
I should feel cold from the water,
but somehow, I feel hot.
My heart is pounding.
Hey! Did you two forget we're here?
Now, now. They worked so hard.
What's the problem?
You're both soaked. I'll dry you off.
It feels so warm and cozy.
Thanks.
Thank you!
Tiara, look.
Oh, what adorable flowers!
It's a new species
that bloomed from your magic.
My magic?
What's this?
There seems to be something in it.
What is it?
It's your flower,
so why don't you open it?
Okay.
What a sweet scent.
Could this be...
Tiara!
Oh, it's fine.
See? It's very sweet, delicious sugar!
I don't know if I should say that's
just what I'd expect from you or...
P-Prince Aqua?!
Yes, your finger is sweet, all right.
Enough! Stop doing things
that make me jealous!
Tiara is my wife!
Oh, really, you two.
Can't you just get along?
You're going?
Yes.
Claire's probably angrier
about all this than anyone.
Unlike me, he actually likes humans.
I'm sure he'll handle it
just fine, though.
He's scary when he's mad, you know.
Keith! This is no laughing matter!
Aw, sure it is.
We can count on Claire to handle Pearl.
We returned the ocean to normal,
but Pearl's heart is still...
I'm going, too.
There may be nothing I can do,
but I want to talk
to King Pearl one more time.
Tiara...
But Pearl's castle is under the sea.
How are you going to see her?
Well...
If you don't mind,
could I come along as well?
Lady Icilla?
I'm an absolute fool
and a horrible person.
I should have known I couldn't change
Your Highness's feelings
with such a potion.
I won't ask you to forgive me.
But if you would grant me one chance,
I will protect Lady Tiararose
with my very life.
So, please... please...
Thank you for offering.
I'll feel much better if you're with us.
Tiara, are you sure about this?
Yes. You can head back to the city.
Put the people at ease with the news
that we've healed the ocean.
Tiara's starting to sound like
a crown princess, isn't she?
Yes, she really is.
We'll be going, then.
I'm sure this wouldn't
have happened at all
if I'd never come to this country.
That's why I have to
see this through to the end.
Including the future of those two...
and the end of this game!
Translation:
Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
Quality Control:
Translation Check:
Rebecca Cottrill
Mariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
Love Is Always and Forever
Tiara, I will always be by your side.
No matter what the future holds,
as long as I'm with you...